[{"answer": "Piers, I get letters in the mail daily from folks who say you are my doctor.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "What's the motivation for you when you have those kind of open, free clinics?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Everyone has to be in the system.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "How does America look after its most needy people with a system that often doesn't allow them to have anything?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Eighty million people.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Eighty million people?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "The simple answer is the most expensive thing we do in medicine is provide bad care.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What's the simple answer?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "It's usually restrictive.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "How restrictive is that to you as a practitioner?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "You know, again, using your scaling system, I would probably give us an 80.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Comparative to, say, other main countries, major countries in the world?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Let me ask you a question -- well, you didn't grow up in this country, but I think our viewers might resonate to this, and so I ask this to you directly -- did you walk to school when you were a kid?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Or pre-op.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Dr. Oz?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "One-thirty-four/eighty-two is average for America.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "So, how good is that?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "One-fifteen over 75 is the optimal number.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "What should I be looking for?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "What an error.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What the hell are you talking about, Dr. Oz?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I'm sure you're about to tell you it's not good for you.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "One example, skim milk, good for you or bad for you if you're going to lose weight?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Drink regular milk, just drink less of it, because it's real food.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "What is the best milk to drink?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Many of the preservatives good for shelf life but they're bad for human life.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "How many preservatives are in this food?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Five major themes that drive 70 percent of how long and how well we age.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What are the biggest problems Americans facing with health they could easily fix, what are the most common mistakes people make with their health?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, first off, carbohydrates, I do think we have a problem with simple carbohydrates, the simple sugars, the white foods, white rice, white pasta, the whites that we bake with, these are all problems for us.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "What is the best way to lose weight without having to just eat carrots?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Your body is geared -- listen, there a dozen systems to keep you eating.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Because it's too dramatic, isn't it?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Just give you an idea of 100 calories, half a doughnut, half a soft drink, a small little nudgy move like that will take off about 12 or 13 pounds a year.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Focus primarily on losing 100 calories a day from the way would you normally lead your life, what kind of results would you see and what kind of time span?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Fifty-one.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "How old are you, if you don't mine me asking?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Which is around 6:00, about 5:00 or 6:00 for reason I come to in a second.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Which is?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Seven.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Seven?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Seven minutes is enough to get you going in the morning, to get your metabolism up, to get my pushups and sit-up with us my stretching exercises, I feel like I control what I'm doing the rest of the day.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Seven minutes is enough?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "So, do you go to the gym at all?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Do you run?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, first, alcohol has a longevity benefit, without question.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "How are you going to deal with my cravings?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "It's absolutely true.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Is it true that red wine is better for you than white wine?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I always have nuts in my pocket.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What are the good things?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I like Walnuts, but I like the taste.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Any nut good?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "There's no way you can block that off.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, most people will have a problem with too much bread.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "What if you absolutely love bread?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Uh, almost all of it.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "How much of it, if you are honest, was shock marketing?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Well, I guess the -- the consideration we took was to -- to prerecord the alternative versions for radio and elsewhere, just in the event that the song, you know, did connect in some way.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "When it goes that big and you've had a bit of fun with the title and it's obviously deliberately shocking, does any part of you slightly feel, well, maybe we should have been a bit more careful here?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "It certainly did that.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "That is with people, you know what I'm saying?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "It's definitely a rude -- a very rude awakening.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "When you're 18 years old and you effectively -- you have now been orphaned, what does that do to a young man?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I think she would have been the best manager ever.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "What do you think she would have made of your extraordinary success?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "I think she still is.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "She would be pretty proud of you, wouldn't she?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes, I think she is definitely alive in all of this positive energy surrounding what's become of me.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Do you feel that she is a constant presence?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Well, I will correct one of those statements.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "What was going on in this mad world that you were then occupying?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "-- sort of slightly out of control?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Is that overstating it?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Well, I definitely -- again, my mother's passing, you know, had a lot to do with me committing myself.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "How did you transform into this Cee Lo?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "That's it.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Would you stop being modest, please?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "You have got two diamonds, right?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "It's about -- a gentleman never tells, but we are friends and we are not -- people talking, right.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Dare I ask how much they are worth?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "If you -- if you are honest with yourself, it is very hard for people to lie to you.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Can you trust women?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "I guess, you know, it would be, you know, a matter of just share and share alike and earning your keep and all of those good old-fashioned quotables that you could apply to the conversation of just, you know, what's fair is fair and blah, blah, blah.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "What are values that make a good America?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "I'm not a big Tweeter.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Are you a big Tweeter?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "I have about a million followers.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "How many followers have you got?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "It makes sense.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "Most certainly, most certainly.", "docId": "120518pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Can you promise that I get an invite if you're going to have the mother of all parties?", "qSentId": 664}]